Hello,
hello friends, welcome to Extra Officer
friends, Apple's launch has begun and
along with this, from next week, the
process of quarterly research will begin. Meaning,
one by one, the quarterly phone results of all the companies will
start coming. In such a situation, it becomes
very important to check the quarterly results of your favorite companies. But those who
are new to the market do not know
where the quarters are checked. They will
either have to watch them on TV news channels
or else
they will have to understand how the
quota of their favorite company has turned out by watching videos on YouTube. That is why
friends, in today's video, we will see
how and from where the quarterly results of any company are
checked. First of all,
come to your browser. I have
come to Google Chrome here because it seems easier to me.
And yes, whether you do it from a mobile
or a computer, the thing is the same, the
system will remain the same, so there is
no need to worry. Now you will
see a stock work here. Simply here you have to
type BSP, BTS stands for
Bombay Stock Exchange. Now see here,
my system has taken this entire link automatically.
If your system doesn't accept it, then simply
search by typing "bloody."
After that, in the results that will appear, you will see the word "
BSE's official website."
Click on it and take it
inside. There will be only one. Now I am
searching here. It will
not take me directly to the official website of BSE.
This was open. The official
website of BSE, I am moving it to the desktop side. It could be
adjusted on the screen. It will
work even if you do it yourself.
Yes, you can see this. There is an
excise box here. Now type the name of the company whose
quarter you want to search
in this search box. I will
write "Infosys" here. Once Info is displayed,
some research results have appeared here, that is, names have
appeared. See, Infosys has also appeared here.
I click on it.
Now this page has loaded and appeared. I will
adjust it a little so that it becomes
easier to view. It should appear a little on the screen.
Yes, this is done, you can
see Infosys. Now you simply have to come down a little here. Yes,
this is what you need.  You can see the announcement. This is the
announcement moment. Here, all the
companies' dates are uploaded in advance along with the country.
If you go inside, that is, if
you click on it,
you will see the time as well. When
any company's quarterly results are released, you will
see them in this announcement area.
For example, Infosys has made some
advancements here, you can read about them on a particular date here. Similarly, at the
time of the results, it will be
written here only. For example,
some related things like the board meeting
note has been reduced or fancy dress will be
written like this, whether it is in the first line or the second, that
means you will see it in this place only.
Now when you see the
call for a board meeting or
pimples, when you see something like this, then
click on it. As soon as
I click here,
see, it has opened on Next.
I will adjust it a little.
Yes, now you will
see a rate symbol on the right side here.
You will have to click on it. Well, here I
would like to say one thing again, this quarter is
not here, you know.  I'm
showing this demo so you can understand.
When you actually do
quarterly research for any company, you'll have to
follow these steps.
Here, it says something like "Stock Incentive Grand-2 Eligible
Employees," but when you
check the water level, you'll find
something like "Quarterly Results" or "Board Meeting Out Confidence Level."
Now, click on this red symbol.
But before that, you should know
what will happen by clicking on this red symbol.
Actually, after clicking on this red ball, a
PDF file will be downloaded. This PDF file is
a change made by the company.
Whenever a company undergoes authentication or
advancement, etc., then the
company files a notice of the changes
and informs them about the action taken or enhancement. We get that notice here
in PDF format. So, if I
click on this number, the
PDF file has been downloaded
and I'm redirected to that PDF file.
If it doesn't redirect you, there's no need to
worry.  No, because that
PDF file has been downloaded in your phone
and is also there, you just have to search a little
in the internal storage of your phone where the PDF file is
stored,
you will find it here. So, we were forced to
download this PDF file of stock incentives,
if we had seen the quarter like this now, then
I would have downloaded it and
explained to you how to read the quarter report,
but never mind, in this video we have learnt so much
that how to reach the quarter finals,
how to download it,
when the quarter report starts coming then we will
make a video on that too so that you can
understand how to read the quarter research,
then friends, if
you liked the information then definitely subscribe to the channel
because on this channel we keep
bringing updates related to the share market, so for
now, that's all we have said
in this video, till then goodbye.